<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>job on Bodacious Blog</title>
    <link>https://mullikine.github.io/tags/job/</link>
    <description>Recent content in job on Bodacious Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +1300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mullikine.github.io/tags/job/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Application to Canva</title>
      <link>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/application-to-canva/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/application-to-canva/</guid>
      <description>Work in progress
To Canva,
Please consider me for the position of Search Infrastructure Software Engineer.
&amp;hellip;
Yours sincerely,
Shane Mulligan
TODO Demonstrate Python AWS Solr ElasticSearch Responsibilities  Design, build out, and support our search platform – the Solr infrastructure, Solr application logic &amp;amp; Search relevance improvements Work with the data-science to power and improve the discovery and search experiences across Canva Ensuring that the millions of public assets that Canva stores are searchable &amp;amp; the right content is delivered to the user at the right time Work cross-functionally with the various platform, technology, and product teams to build out the next generation of high-availability and scalable search capability Build and maintain internal tooling for logging, monitoring, load testing, alerting and reporting needs for our search infrastructure Developing solutions you’ve designed from the ground up through from conception to deployment into production Performance in debugging, benchmarking, and addressing Identifying and addressing performance bottlenecks Canva’s search infrastructure Design meetings; code reviews; mentoring new starters; technical interviews; and contributing to growing the team  Required Skills and Background  Five-plus (5+) years of commercial software development experience writing high-performance production-quality code in Python and Bash (experience with Java is a plus, but not required) Extensive experience with Apache Solr or ElasticSearch Experience developing complex cloud-based search applications and infrastructure at scale Broad knowledge of Cloud (AWS), Networking, and OS (Linux) concepts, services, and best practices Firmly grounded computer science and engineering fundamentals including concurrency, multithreading, data structures, solution design, architecture, and design patterns Be self-driven, able to take ownership of projects, and be able to think in terms of systems, process, and business value, not just technology  Search engines Croogle Demonstration of CroogleRTC Search Engine - YouTube</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Application for DevOps Engineer</title>
      <link>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/job-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/job-application/</guid>
      <description>Phone Email City     +64 21 1462 759 mullikine@gmail.com Dunedin, NZ    .org-center { margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; text-align: center; }  Platform Engineering · Software Engineering · Test Automation · Natural Language Processing
 Shane Mulligan [Cover Letter] Dear Hiring Manager, Please consider me for this role. I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about developing tooling and automating software development processes. In 2020 I contracted for FMG in Australia developing CI/CD infrastructure their vehicle autonomy team on AWS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>★ Application to Fortescue Metals Group ★</title>
      <link>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/application-to-fortescue-metals-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/application-to-fortescue-metals-group/</guid>
      <description>Other formats Word application-to-fortescue-metals-group.doc PDF application-to-fortescue-metals-group.pdf  To Fortescue Metals Group,
Please consider me for the position of Senior Software Tester.
In the specific area of HIL Testing I have 2 years of solid experience from working at Crown Robotics Technology Center ( RTC ) in Penrose, Auckland. I also have a year of building and testing a C++ application for TracMap (details below). I have also accrued a significant amount of testing experience over the last 8 years working as a Software Engineer on embedded software, software as a service (SASS) and continuous integration (CI) as a service.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>