<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>games on Bodacious Blog</title>
    <link>https://mullikine.github.io/tags/games/</link>
    <description>Recent content in games on Bodacious Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mullikine.github.io/tags/games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>(WIP) How to play Dwarf Fortress (in fortress mode)</title>
      <link>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/dwarf-fortress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/dwarf-fortress/</guid>
      <description>https://df-walkthrough.readthedocs.io/en/latest/
Navigating left hand should sit on keys 1 to 4. right hand should sit on keys 6 to 9.
pinkies navigate bottom left to top right. index fingers navigate top left to bottom right
Memorise them as they may be useful They are also useful in brogue. They may also be useful in other programs. I can memorise them and then use them in all sorts of situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hitchhiker&#39;s Guide To The Galaxy – The Infocom Game, on Ubuntu, in a terminal!</title>
      <link>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/hhgttg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/hhgttg/</guid>
      <description>Setup cd git clone &amp;#34;https://gitlab.com/DavidGriffith/frotz&amp;#34; git clone &amp;#34;https://github.com/historicalsource/hitchhikersguide&amp;#34; apt install libao-dev apt install libsndfile-dev apt install libsamplerate-dev apt install libmodplug-dev Play ~/frotz/frotz ~/hitchhikersguide/COMPILED/s4.z3 Recording of hhgttg running</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best emacs tetris in emacs 26&#43;</title>
      <link>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/emacs-tetris-nice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/emacs-tetris-nice/</guid>
      <description>emacs 27 has an update to emacs&amp;rsquo; tetris mode which makes the glyphs display larger on higher DPI screens.
This script will download that update from git.savannah.gnu.org and display tetris in a distraction free environment for the ultimate productivity.
Symlinks If you symlink this script to etetris-vt100 and run that instead, you will get the animated and striking black and white terminal version.
ln -s etetris etetris-vt100 If you symlink this script to etetris-xterm and run that instead, you will get the vivid color terminal version.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>