<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>graphviz on Bodacious Blog</title>
    <link>https://mullikine.github.io/tags/graphviz/</link>
    <description>Recent content in graphviz on Bodacious Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +1200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mullikine.github.io/tags/graphviz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Generate graphviz and prolog from org-brain</title>
      <link>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/generate-graphviz-and-prolog-from-org-brain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/generate-graphviz-and-prolog-from-org-brain/</guid>
      <description>Summary I would like to be creating graphs interactively with org-brain and then using them to generate graphviz, plantuml and mermaid diagrams, and also knowledge bases with prolog.
Why Prolog? Prolog is incredibly useful for querying KBs. If I plan on working for a large corporation with their own ontologies and knowledge graphs, then I will want to be skilled with Prolog.
Graphviz  --  A generated graphviz neato diagram This has been generated from an org-brain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graphviz and Hugo</title>
      <link>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/graphviz/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/graphviz/</guid>
      <description>See also:  The worlds fastest framework for building websites | Hugo Generate graphviz and prolog from org-brain // Bodacious Blog Babel: active code in Org-mode    Summary This is just a demonstration of how I put graphs in my blog. I am using Hugo, the static site builder, org-mode, a file format for writing notes in emacs and org-babel, the builtin extension for org-mode for embedding code blocks in org files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compounding Confoundment: arbitrary interpreters for Babel</title>
      <link>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/arbitrary-interpreters-for-babel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/arbitrary-interpreters-for-babel/</guid>
      <description>Genesis 11:7 “&amp;hellip;Come, let us go down and confuse their language so they will not understand each other.” If supporting many languages in Babel was not confounding enough, lets support arbitrary interpreters too!  The need to specify a custom interpreter arose when I needed to provide my own interpreter for generating an ASCII graph from a dot script.
Objective Specify an :interpreter and/or :filter command to override the execute behaviour.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
