<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ci on Bodacious Blog</title>
    <link>https://mullikine.github.io/tags/ci/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ci on Bodacious Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mullikine.github.io/tags/ci/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>k3sup, bootstrap a lightweight k8s</title>
      <link>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/k3sup-bootstrap-a-lightweight-k8s/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/k3sup-bootstrap-a-lightweight-k8s/</guid>
      <description>Source material Rancher Docs: Quick-Start Guide GitHub - alexellis/k3sup: bootstrap Kubernetes with k3s over SSH &amp;lt; 1 min  k3s is great for CI Perhaps it will make its way into Gitlab CI. Surely, a k8s of some implementation will.
Set up k3s &amp;ndash; lightweight kubernetes This is a dependency.
1 2 3  curl -sfL https://get.k3s.io | sh - # Check for Ready node, takes maybe 30 seconds k3s kubectl get node   https://k3s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hydra - CI and release management for NixOS</title>
      <link>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/nix-hydra-ci/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/nix-hydra-ci/</guid>
      <description>Original article https://nixos.org/hydra/manual/  1 2 3 4  big bang integration The phenomenon where components are only tested together near the end of the development process.   Background Continuous Integration An automated system continuously or periodically:
 check out the source code of a project, build it, run tests, and produce reports for the developers.  CI Tools enable Lenthy tests Many projects have very large test sets (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CodeQL by GitHub and Semmle</title>
      <link>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/codeql-by-github-and-semmle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/codeql-by-github-and-semmle/</guid>
      <description>Reference material Getting started with the CodeQL CLI - CodeQL QL packs - CodeQL Related articles CodeLingo vs Linters: TLDR // Bodacious Blog  Glossary 1 2 3  QL pack Contains important metadata that tells the CodeQL CLI how to process the query files.   Step 1) Install the CLI Releases github/codeql-cli-binaries GitHub
Step 2) Obtain a local copy of the CodeQL queries 1 2 3 4 5 6 7  # Download the following repositories git clone https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview of modern Continuous Integration tools</title>
      <link>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/review-of-continuous-integration-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/review-of-continuous-integration-tools/</guid>
      <description>Circle CI Trust your CI/CD pipeline. Push code with confidence.
Automate your development process quickly, safely, and at scale.
Codeship Check in your code. Let us handle the rest. We provide a simple, turn-key SaaS CI/CD platform that is fast and flexible so that you can hit the ground running and build stuff that matters.
Runs the tests and deploys.
It replaces Circle CI.
Travis Easily sync your GitHub projects with Travis CI and you’ll be testing your code in minutes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of CI tools for emacs</title>
      <link>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/continuous-integration-emacs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/continuous-integration-emacs/</guid>
      <description>Summary I look at the following emacs plugins:
   Plugin Last update     magit-circleci 20191209.2113   magit-gh-pulls 20191230.1944   magit-gitflow 20170929.824   jenkins 20200524.2016   jenkins-watch 20121004.2326   travis 20150825.1138   org-link-travis 20140405.2327   magit-circleci 20191209.2113    magit-circleci Magit extension to integrate with CircleCI. See the latest builds from the magit status buffer.
magit-gh-pulls These are the bindings for pull requests, defined in magit-gh-pulls-mode-map:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
