<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CI on Bodacious Blog</title>
    <link>https://mullikine.github.io/tags/ci/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CI on Bodacious Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mullikine.github.io/tags/ci/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CodeQL by GitHub and Semmle</title>
      <link>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/codeql-by-github-and-semmle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/codeql-by-github-and-semmle/</guid>
      <description>Reference material Getting started with the CodeQL CLI - CodeQL QL packs - CodeQL Related articles CodeLingo vs Linters: TLDR // Bodacious Blog  Glossary 1 2 3  QL pack Contains important metadata that tells the CodeQL CLI how to process the query files.   Install the CLI Releases github/codeql-cli-binaries GitHub
Obtain a local copy of the CodeQL queries Using my xsh script, which is like bash but works over interactive subshells.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview of modern Continuous Integration tools</title>
      <link>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/review-of-continuous-integration-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/review-of-continuous-integration-tools/</guid>
      <description>Circle CI Trust your CI/CD pipeline. Push code with confidence.
Automate your development process quickly, safely, and at scale.
Codeship Check in your code. Let us handle the rest. We provide a simple, turn-key SaaS CI/CD platform that is fast and flexible so that you can hit the ground running and build stuff that matters.
Runs the tests and deploys.
It replaces Circle CI.
Travis Easily sync your GitHub projects with Travis CI and you’ll be testing your code in minutes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of CI tools for emacs</title>
      <link>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/continuous-integration-emacs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/continuous-integration-emacs/</guid>
      <description> Emacs plugins  plugin list  magit-circleci magit-gh-pulls magit-gitflow jenkins jenkins-watch travis org-link-travis magit-circleci   Demonstration of jenkins.el for emacs 
TODO Review these jenkins plugins  plugin list  folders OWASP markup formatter build timeout crenditials binding timestamper workspace cleanup ant gradle pipeline github branch source pipeline: github groovy libraries pipeline: stage view git subversion ssh slaves matrix authorization strategy PAM authentication LDAP Email extension mailer   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>