<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tmux on Bodacious Blog</title>
    <link>https://mullikine.github.io/tags/tmux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tmux on Bodacious Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mullikine.github.io/tags/tmux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Searching awesome lists for curated web browsing</title>
      <link>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/curated-surfing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/curated-surfing/</guid>
      <description>Here I demonstrate searching through and reading lists of things from the command line.
I ran into some issues with the googlesearch pip module It seems to have been taken down from pip.
I changed my script to use emacs&amp;rsquo; eww browser to scrape the results instead eww is pretty reliable.
Demonstration Please be patient as I bypass the problem above.

Some search results from the demonstration above http://linear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meta &amp; Inception</title>
      <link>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/meta-inception/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/meta-inception/</guid>
      <description>This is a blog article about writing a blog article about recording myself recording myself playing tetris inside emacs inside tmux inside neovim inside spacemacs, inside the 5 nested tmux sessions seen at the bottom of the screen.
DONE tetris inside of emacs etetris-vt100 DONE tetris inside of neovim terminal inside of tmux nvt etetris-vt100 DONE tetris inside of neovim terminal inside of tmux inside of spacemacs sp -sh nvt etetris-vt100 DONE asciinema recording of an asciinema recording of tetris inside of neovim terminal inside of tmux inside of spacemacs Meta inception</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>