<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>deployment on Bodacious Blog</title>
    <link>https://mullikine.github.io/tags/deployment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in deployment on Bodacious Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mullikine.github.io/tags/deployment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>OS-agnostic program installation with Ansible</title>
      <link>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/os-agnostic-program-installation-with-ansible/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/os-agnostic-program-installation-with-ansible/</guid>
      <description>Ansible setup https://github.com/ansible/ansible Original guide How to install apps remotely with Ansible - TechRepublic Related articles Ansible // Bodacious Blog   1 2 3 4  sudo apt update sudo apt install software-properties-common sudo apt-add-repository --yes --update ppa:ansible/ansible sudo apt install ansible   Set up ssh Get the IP of the instance 1 2  aws ec2 describe-instances --output json | jq -r &amp;#39;.Reservations[].Instances[].NetworkInterfaces[].Association.PublicIp&amp;#39;   54.206.107.77 Set the Host options 1 2 3 4  Host littlefella Hostname 54.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of &#39;Ansible and Terraform: Better Together&#39;</title>
      <link>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/review-of-ansible-and-terraform-better-together/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/review-of-ansible-and-terraform-better-together/</guid>
      <description>Original article Ansible and Terraform: Better Together  Why do you need more than Ansible? Ansible doesn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily have to own and do every single task that it sets out to do; Like an instrument in an orchestra, others may be better positioned for particular tasks.
Ansible Vault vs Terraform Vault I would assume, since Terraform is a Hashicorp product, then the recommended secret solution would their Vault.
1  ewwlinks +/&amp;#34;The Vault provider allows Terraform to read from, write to, and configure Hashicorp Vault.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deployment with IaC and Octopus</title>
      <link>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/deployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 00:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/deployment/</guid>
      <description>1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17  OTA deployment over-the-air deployment Over-the-Air programming OTA Refers to various methods of distributing new software, configuration settings, and even updating encryption keys to devices like mobile phones, set-top boxes or secure voice communication equipment (encrypted 2-way radios). codeship A fast and secure hosted CI service that scales with your needs. It supports GitHub, Bitbucket, and Gitlab projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autoscaling GitLab Runner on AWS</title>
      <link>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/autoscaling-gitlab-runner-on-aws/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mullikine.github.io/posts/autoscaling-gitlab-runner-on-aws/</guid>
      <description>Summary I design and put together an autoscaling GitLab Runner solution (which scales using EC2 Spot instances), along with a price analysis of options, for deploying ROS2 application source code to GitLab to be built and further deployed.
Creating this article and enabling AWS glossary  Glossary of GitLab CI/CD http://github.com/mullikine/glossaries-gh/blob/master/gitlab.txt   --  I automated the digestion of this reading material  [10/10] Read and done  https://docs.gitlab.com/runner/configuration/autoscale.html https://packages.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
